Samuel Armstrong

Front-End Developer

CONTACT



0210 814 1871



armstrong.samuelm @gmail.com



13A Jasper Ave Mt Roskill Auckland 1041

About

Self-taught front end developer, with a passion for technology, people and experiences. A lifetime of experience understanding, troubleshooting and problem solving and a solid set of development skills to match.

Skills	
Responsive Design JavaScript Node.js, NPM and tooling React + Redux Version control Back-end and database (Express, MongoDB, GraphQL)	Excellent communication Proven customer service skills Strong Analytical/Critical thinking Conflict Resolution Self Motivation Willingness to take criticism Continual drive for self-improvement

Employment History

Electrical Tool Services

March 2018 - Present

Electrical Service Technician

Troubleshooting, repair and maintenance of electrical, mechanical and electronic tools and systems

Four Seasons Resort

June 2016 - November 2018

Senior Cocktail Bartender

World recognized customer service, menu development and leadership role in a small team

Education

The University of Western Australia

2005 - 2012

Bachelor of Engineering (Petroleum)

Bachelor of Commerce (Managment)